const data = [
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "How was the discipline of product design born?",
    answer:
      "The discipline of “product design” was born from this movement to deliver beautiful and useful products to people that otherwise may not be able to afford them.",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "What does the term ‘product’ encompass”?",
    answer:
      "In the digital age, the term “product” encompasses both hardware and software. It all about experiences that users have in the physical world. They aim to solve a problems in people’s everyday lives.",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "What is product design?",
    answer:
      "Product design is the whole product experience.  It could mean designing a mobile app, a web app, a website, a dashboard, branding, or all of the above.",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "What is a misconception about product design?",
    answer:
      "An unfortunate misconception is that product design exists to make products look pretty.",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "How could you describe a holistic approach to product design?",
    answer:
      "It’s a method of creating, iterating, and testing your solutions to make the user’s experience better.",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "What is the product designer’s responsibility?",
    answer:
      "Product designer’s responsibility to create a consistent end-to-end experience.",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "What has been considered the holy grail of innovation?",
    answer: "Design thinking",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "What is design thinking?",
    answer:
      "Design thinking focuses on achieving practical results and solutions",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question:
      "What should the practical results and solutions of design thinking be?",
    answer: "Technically possible, Economically viable, Desirable by the user",
  },
  {
    category: "Digital Product and Design",
    question: "What are the five steps of the design thinking process?",
    answer: "Empathize, Define, Ideate, Prototype, Test",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "What is user-centered design?",
    answer:
      "User-centered design is an iterative design process framework that incorporates validation from the user every step of the way.",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "Why is user-centered design useful?",
    answer:
      "That helps deeply understand your user, what they want and don’t want from your design, and how they’re going to interact with each part of your product.",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "What are the four steps of the user-centered design process?",
    answer:
      "Identify the users, Specify requirements for business and user, Design solutions, Evaluate.",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "What is user-research about?",
    answer:
      "It’s about: Who is my user? What are my users’ problems? What are they about?",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "What are two types of requirements?",
    answer: "Business requirements, User requirements.",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "What is the big why?",
    answer:
      "Why is this design beneficial for both the business and the user? Why is it worth your time to do it right now?",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "What assets does the designer build?",
    answer: "Site map, Wireframes, Prototypes, Mock-ups, Images, Icons, Colors",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "How do you evaluate your designs?",
    answer:
      "Some questions I might ask: Where did our process go right? Why?,  Where did we struggle? Why?, How are our users responding to the product?, Did it solve their issues and pain points?, Where can we improve the product?, What lessons can we take away from this process for future products?",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question: "What is meant by 'iteration'?",
    answer:
      "That means going back to step one and starting the user-centered design process over — but with the knowledge you gained in the first round.",
  },
  {
    category: "User-Centered Design",
    question:
      "What is the ultimate goal of the whole process of user-centered design?",
    answer:
      "The ultimate goal is to create product deeply connected to the user needs and understand the user you are working with",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "What is user experience?",
    answer:
      "It’s the overall experience a user has when interacting with a product or service in a given context.",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "Is UX limited to the digital space?",
    answer:
      "UX isn’t limited to the digital space. Anything that can be experienced can be designed.",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "Why is UX such an exciting field?",
    answer:
      "The impact of good (and bad!) UX is everywhere, and we already know a lot more about UX than we realize.",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question:
      "What characteristics of the product are taken into account when evaluating its user experience?",
    answer: "Ease of use, quality, and efficiency.",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "What do UX designers look to do?",
    answer:
      "UX designers look to bridge the gap between the product and the human user. To make product intuitive and straightforward as possible",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "What are some applications for UX design?",
    answer:
      "Website, App And Software Design; Voice Design; Virtual Reality (VR) and Augmented Reality (AR)",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "What value does UX bring from a user perspective?",
    answer:
      "From a user perspective, good UX design enables us to go about our daily lives as effortlessly as possible.",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "How do you understand inclusive design?",
    answer:
      "How UX designers can bring value to all kinds of users. Otherwise inclusive design is known as universal or accessible design.",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "What backgrounds do UX designers come from?",
    answer: "Visual design, programming, psychology and interaction design.",
  },
  {
    category: "User Experience Design",
    question: "What are the typical tasks of the UX designer?",
    answer:
      "A UX designer’s typical tasks often include user research, creating personas, designing wireframes and interactive prototypes as well as testing designs.",
  },
];

export default data;
